Loretta J. Ross Papers, 1956-2005
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES VII. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS, The video and audio tapes from the Loretta Ross Papers have been digitized and are available online (Smith campus access only)
  - Videotapes, Videotapes from the Loretta Ross Papers have been digitized and are available online (Smith campus access only)
    - Speaking Out For Reproductive Freedom 1991 (2) (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Feminist Expo 2000, General Assembly III (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - "Women in America," Loretta Ross, Simpson College, Indianola IA 1996 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Color of Violence 2000 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Rights and Wrongs Show #302-Children 1995 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Reflections of a Partnership, WHARP (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Camp Sister Spirit, Loretta Ross 1996 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Loretta Ross, Workshop #1 and 2, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Southern Human Rights Organizing Conference, (CHRE) 1996 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Between Ourselves: NOW Reproductive Rights Conference, (Summary) 1987 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Legislating for Reproductive Rights/workshop #2, Right wing attacks against reproductive freedom 1987 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - NCAAS Day 1989 (4) (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Loretta Ross, Ithaca College 1998 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Donahue Show, Black Women and Feminism, (Loretta Ross, Byllye Avery, Paula Giddings, and Barbara Smith) 1989 (2) (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Newstalk Television, afternoon segment 1995 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - "Ageism and battering for women of color," Loretta Ross, BIHA Women in Action 1989 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Face the Hate (TV program) (also has "Batman" on it) (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - "Christian Identity" (pro-lifer) and Randall Terry visit 1993 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - "Ship of Friends": 20th Anniversary celebrations of the 1967 Al-Fateh Revolution in LibyaSep 1987 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Global Village or Global Pillage? Narrated by Ed Asner undated (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Odyssey Weekly, Show 2041, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Narrowcasting: Technology and the Rise of the Christian Right 1996 (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - When Love Hurts 1993 (2) (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - The Leader, His Driver and the Driver's Wife 1991 (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - Abortion for Survival undated (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - "The 90s" (What watching TV does to us) undated (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - "Bring Human Rights Home," Loretta Ross, Making a Difference Conference 2001 (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - NOW: Celebrating 20 Years 1986 (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Video, Hi8
    - National Center for Human Rights Education, Retreat (7)1997 (Box 60, Folder 31)
- SERIES VIII. MEMORABILIA
  - Awards 1982-94 (Box 61)
  - Miscellaneous 1987, undated (Box 61)
  - Buttons (Box 62)
  - Rolodex and address cards undated (Box 63)
  - Phone messages and business cards (Box 64)
- SERIES IX. PERIODICALS
  - Aegis 1978-86 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Africa News 1989-90 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Africa USA 1989 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - African Commentary 1989-99 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Amicus Journal 1992-94 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Black Issues in Higher Education 1995 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Black Scholar 1979-84 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Bottom Fish Blues 1987 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - CARE Briefs undated (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Catholic League Newsletter 1991-92 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Communigu'Elles 1986-88 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Conscience 1992-93 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Drumbeat 1988 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Echo 1986-87 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Emerge 1990-93 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Essence 1985-86 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Feminist Alliance Against Rape, FAAR News. 1976-78 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Focus 1985-89 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Focus on the Family 1993-94 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Health/PAC Bulletin 1991-92 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Friends for Jamaica Newsletter 1984 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Insurgent 1986-87 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Militant 1979-87 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Nation 1995 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - National Alliance 1987 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - New Directions for Women 1987-88 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Noticias de la Semana (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Off Our Backs 1986-93 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - On The Issues 1993-94 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Out Write 1986-88 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - People's Perspective 1993 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Policy Focus 1984-86 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Sage 1984-87 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Seeds 1980 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Sisterlife 1987-88 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Sojourner 1988-95 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Southern Exposure 1980-90 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Spotlight 1994 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Unity 1987 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Upfront 1986-89 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Witness 1986-89 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Women of the World 1988 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - WREE View of Women for Racial and Economic Equality 1983-88 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, A-Y (Box 68, Folder 2-6)
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  - UN Conference of Population and Development, Cairo: Posters, 1994 (Map-case Flat File)